{"data":[{"question":"Your boyfriend has _______ phoned _______ written.","a":"either\/nor","b":"neither\/nor","c":"either\/or","d":"neither\/or","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Neither ... nor ...:  used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She didn't see _______ of the boys.","a":"neither","b":"either","c":"nor","d":"both","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Either: used to begin a list of two or more possibilities","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"_______ you go _______ I go.","a":"Either\/or","b":"Either\/nor","c":"Neither\/nor","d":"Neither\/or","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Either\/or: used to begin a list of two or more possibilities","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Both were cheap, but I didn't like _______.","a":"neither","b":"both","c":"either","d":"none","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Either: is used in negative sentences to add an agreeing thought","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"_______ Leslie and Jean came at seven o'clock.","a":"Neither","b":"Either","c":"Nor","d":"Both","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Both: used to talk about two people, things... together","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Your brother left a week ago but he has ________ written ________ phoned.","a":"either\/or","b":"neither\/nor","c":"neither\/or","d":"either\/nor","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Neither ... nor ...: used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"We entered the room and found it _________ hot and humid.","a":"both","b":"either","c":"neither","d":"nor","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Both: used to talk about two people, things... together\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She tried on the two skirts but _________ was big enough.","a":"either","b":"neither","c":"both","d":"none","answer":"2","explain":"\nNeither: used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"There were six or seven ties but ________ them suited me.","a":"none of","b":"none","c":"neither of","d":"either of","answer":"1","explain":"\n- None of: not any amount of something or not one of a group of people or things","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The room was _______ bright _______ large.","a":"neither\/nor","b":"either\/or","c":"neither\/or","d":"either\/nor","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Neither ... nor ...:  used when mentioning two things that are not true or possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}